{
    "subject": "resource/Tommy_Tutone",
    "predicate": "property/pastMembers",
    "object": "Greg Sutton",
    "human_readable": "Greg Sutton was a past member of Tommy Tutone.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9837328791618347,
            "question": "Was Greg Sutton a current member of Tommy Tutone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9667509198188782,
            "question": "Was Tommy Tutone a former band that Greg Sutton was in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9005041122436523,
            "question": "Is Greg Sutton still performing with Tommy Tutone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8252703547477722,
            "question": "Name one band that Greg Sutton was part of."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8103116750717163,
            "question": "In what musical group did Greg Sutton have a past role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8053550720214844,
            "question": "Who was Greg Sutton associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6537280678749084,
            "question": "What is the name of the band Greg Sutton used to be a member of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5973432064056396,
            "question": "What type of artist was Greg Sutton?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5235173106193542,
            "question": "To what musical group did Greg Sutton belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.521571695804596,
            "question": "What band did Greg Sutton play in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Greg Sutton was a past member of Tommy Tutone.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7412_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To what musical group did Greg Sutton belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7412_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of artist was Greg Sutton?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7412_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the band Greg Sutton used to be a member of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7412_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7412_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7412_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7412_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7412_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7412_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7412_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7412_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7412_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7412_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7412_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The context information mentions that after drummer Victor Carberry left, Greg Sutton replaced him as the bassist in Tommy Tutone. This supports the statement that Greg Sutton was a past member of Tommy Tutone."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}